It's time for our group chat topic of the week we ask folks to rep their city
let's go to the phones. Hey Amanda we appreciate you here in Philadelphia we
have to talk about the Philly cheesesteak we also got the pretzels and we have the
water ice. Now I gotta tell you in Philly is gonna be like get her out of here never
been a fan of the cheesesteak never been a fan never been I love water ice yeah
water ice is straight. And Philly I feel like has produced some of the best
musicians like when I was doing music like the best drummers always from Philly
go to our second caller. Calling to rep my city from Boston we got a new edition got
Malcolm X but most of all like Boston is known for education and I think that's
what makes it unique it's like. Okay all right all right all right who else we got on the line?
Star coming from Rochester New York our city is known for Wegmans the grocery
store. I had never heard of Wagmans but when I was at SUNY Purchase presenting an
award in my name they had Wagmans Fuji apple juice in the dressing room and I
literally like now that she's saying it I'm like I had Wagmans Fuji apple juice
cuz I was like where's this from? Wagmans what's that? Now we know. I just feel
like when you're from like New York or LA you be like I mean what's your city got?
But every city got its own thing.